angelsoft.net 2010-12-17

# Privacy Policy | Angelsoft

Angelsoft is committed to protecting your privacy. Maintaining the trust of our users is key to the success of our business, and this Privacy Policy is intended to clearly explain our practices so you can feel confident using our services. Please take the time to read the Angelsoft Privacy Policy below. This Policy explains Angelsoft's privacy practices for Angelsoft.net and the entire Angelsoft platform. It includes what type of personal information is collected, how that information is used, and with whom the information may be shared. If you have any questions regarding this policy, please [contact Angelsoft](https://angelsoft.net/a/contact-form). 

This Privacy Policy is a part of the Terms of Service for the Angelsoft platform. By agreeing to the Terms of Service and using the Angelsoft platform, you agree to be bound by the terms described in this Privacy Policy. Any disputes that arise over privacy between a user and Angelsoft are subject to the provisions of this Policy and the Terms of Service for the Angelsoft platform, which is available at [http://angelsoft.net/a/tos](https://angelsoft.net/a/tos). 

###  **Table of Contents**

  * What is "Personal Data"? 
  * What kind of Personal Data is collected? 
  * What will my Personal Data be used for? 
  * Will any third parties ever see my Personal Data? 
  * Can I get my Personal Data if I leave Angelsoft? 
  * What is Aggregated Data, and how is it used? 
  * What is Website Data, and how is it used? 
  * Who collects information? 
  * What security measures are in place to protect my data? 
  * When will Angelsoft contact me? 
  * Legal Disclaimers 
  * Changes to the Privacy Policy 
  * Contacting Angelsoft 

###  What is "Personal Data"? 

"Personal data" is information about you or your angel group that is personally identifiable and is not otherwise publicly available, including, for example, your name, contact information, and the deals you have participated in. 

Personal data does not include website data or aggregated data. For our policies regarding "Website Data" and "Aggregated Data", please see the "What is Website Data, and how is it used?" and "What is Aggregated Data, and how is it used?" sections of this policy. 

Back to Top

###  What kind of Personal Data is collected? 

When you set up your account with Angelsoft, you will be required to provide certain personal data including your name and email address. Individual angel groups may also require entrepreneurs to enter detailed information about their company. 

You may also be asked to provide other optional personal data like a brief biography, address and phone number. When you interact with the Angelsoft platform, for example by sending a message or uploading a document, this information is also stored on Angelsoft's secure servers. 

Back to Top

###  What will my Personal Data be used for? 

Angelsoft uses your personal data to maintain your account and to provide you with the angel group management and deal collaboration services that serve as the core of the Angelsoft platform. Angelsoft will NEVER use your personal data for any use other than that for which it is submitted without your prior consent. 

Back to Top

###  Will any third parties ever see my Personal Data? 

Under certain business or legal conditions, Angelsoft may have to disclose your personal data to others. 

  * **Affiliated Third Parties**  
Angelsoft may employ or engage other companies and individuals to perform necessary business functions on behalf of Angelsoft (e.g. outside contractors or service providers). If it is necessary to perform these functions these persons may be provided with personal data, but will be prohibited by contract from using this information for any other purpose other than providing the required services. 
  * **Legally Required Disclosure**  
Under certain circumstances, disclosure of your personal data may be required by law. Angelsoft may disclose your information if, in its own best judgment, it is required to do so in order to comply with a judicial or governmental subpoena, warrant, or other order, or to a government institution that has asserted its lawful authority to obtain the information. 
  * **Change of Ownership**  
In the event that ownership of Angelsoft was to change as a result of a merger, acquisition or transfer to another company, your personal data may be transferred. If such a transfer takes place, you will be notified of any material changes to the Privacy Policy. 

Back to Top

###  Can I get my Personal Data if I leave Angelsoft? 

If a group chooses to leave the Angelsoft platform, Angelsoft will provide that group with a copy of all the personal data it has entered into the system. This data will be exported from our system in a format readable by any standard SQL database. 

Upon a user's request, Angelsoft will provide a reasonable description of that user's personal data maintained by Angelsoft. If you wish to receive such a description, please contact us at [support@angelsoft.net](mailto:support@angelsoft.net). 

Back to Top

###  What is Aggregated Data, and how is it used? 

Aggregated data is information that will only be collected in a non-identifiable format and may be combined with other non-identifiable information. 

Angelsoft uses aggregated data to generate accurate metrics about the early stage private equity industry. This information is packaged and sold to third parties such as governments, economic development agencies, and financial institutions. This information is used and analyzed only in the aggregate, and does not contain any personally identifiable personal data. Angelsoft maintains the right to use this information without limitation. 

Back to Top

###  What is Website Data, and how is it used? 

Website data is information that is not about an individual or specific group; rather, it is information about the overall traffic to our website. Examples include the number of visitors to the Angelsoft.net web site and the number of registered users of the Angelsoft platform. Angelsoft may extract and use such web traffic data for purposes including, but not limited to, traffic analysis and business decision making. The statistics generated in this manner contain no personal data and cannot be used to gather any information about individual visitors to the site. 

Angelsoft may also use non-identifying "cookies" to provide you with easier site navigation. A cookie is a small amount of data sent to a user's web browser from a web server, which is then stored on the user's hard drive. Angelsoft's cookies do not generate any personal data, do not read personal data from your computer and are never tied to any personally identifiable information. 

Back to Top

###  Who collects information? 

Angelsoft LLC owns and operates the Angelsoft.net web site and the Angelsoft service platform. Our mailing address is 30 East 23rd Street, New York, NY 10010 and our customer service email address is [support@angelsoft.net](mailto:support@angelsoft.net). 

Back to Top

###  What security measures are in place to protect my data? 

Angelsoft is committed to ensuring the integrity of our users' data and has adopted industry-leading practices to safeguard your personal information from both disclosure and loss. In order to best provide for data integrity, our users' data is stored in a secure facility under controlled environmental conditions. The data is protected by both physical and biometric security measures. All data is stored on redundant systems and is backed up daily to an off-site facility. 

All of Angelsoft's employees that may come into contact with your personal information are under strict contractual obligations to neither disclose your information to any non-affiliated third parties nor to use your information for any purpose that is not necessary to provide you with our services. 

Angelsoft uses industry standard technological means to protect your personal information. We use encryption and a comprehensive authentication protocol, among other technical measures, to provide the best possible level of security. However, please remember that no security system on the Internet is "perfect." 

Back to Top

###  When will Angelsoft contact me? 

Angelsoft will communicate with you in response to your requests for service or customer support. We will contact you either by phone or by email, according to your preference. 

Angelsoft will send you service-related emails if it becomes necessary to do so. For example, if the Angelsoft Platform will be unavailable for a short time due to system maintenance, we may notify you via email. 

Angelsoft may also send you an email in order to notify you of updates to our Privacy Policy, Terms of Service, or other agreement you have with Angelsoft. 

Back to Top

###  Legal Disclaimers 

Angelsoft may provide links to other web sites. Angelsoft is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of these sites. In order to safeguard your privacy, please review the privacy policies of any sites you may visit before providing any Personal Information to them. 

This Privacy Policy only applies to your relationship with Angelsoft. It does not apply to the interactions you have with any other individual or group. In particular, the administrator of your group has the ability to share information you submit to the Angelsoft platform (usually with other group members). Angelsoft is not responsible for any disclosure made by any of these other users of the Angelsoft platform. Your privacy among your group is governed solely by any agreements you may have with that group and is beyond the scope of this Privacy Policy. 

Angelsoft exercises reasonable efforts to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal information; however, transmissions protected by industry standard technology and administered by humans cannot be guaranteed to be absolutely secure. Angelsoft will not be liable for unauthorized disclosure of personal information that occurs through no fault of Angelsoft including, but not limited to, errors in transmission and the unauthorized acts of Angelsoft's employees. 

Angelsoft does not provide products or services for individuals under the age of 18. We neither collect nor maintain information from users actually known to be under the age of 18. 

Back to Top

###  Changes to the Privacy Policy 

Angelsoft uses your personal data to maintain your account and to provide you with the angel group management and deal collaboration services that serve as the core of the Angelsoft platform. Angelsoft will NEVER use your personal data for any use other than that for which it is submitted without your prior consent. 

Back to Top

###  Contacting Angelsoft 

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, or believe that its terms have not been complied with, please  [email Angelsoft](mailto:support@angelsoft.net). 

Back to Top

Policy last updated May 1, 2007  
© 2010 Angelsoft, Inc. All rights reserved.
